Batman Beyond is a action, animation, science
fiction film directed by Darwyn Cooke.
This short celebrating 75 years of Batman from artist Darwyn Cooke returns fans to the world of Batman
Beyond as Terry McGinnis' futuristic Dark Knight faces his most formidable foe of all - himself.
Terry McGinnis / Batman (voice), played by Will Friedle.
Bruce Wayne (voice), played by Kevin Conroy.
The DC Animated Universe (DCAU, also referred to as the Timmverse or Diniverse by fans) is a shared
fictional universe based on DC Comics properties and media franchise produced by Warner Bros.
It began with Batman: The Animated Series in 1992
and ended with Justice League vs.
the Fatal Five in 2019.
The associated media franchise includes theatrical and direct-to-video feature films,
shorts, comic books, video games, and other multimedia adaptations.
The DC Animated Universe has been praised for its storytelling, voice acting, animation, and maturity,
with several of its shows listed among the greatest animated television series of all time.
It has also influenced the mainstream DC Comics in various ways, such as
introducing new characters, revamped backstories, and character designs.
The film explores themes of future, superhero,
based on comic, futuristic, robot.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.